77tracking.com 2016-06-24

# PRIVACY & SECURITY POLICY G

                                 PRIVACY & SECURITY POLICY
GUIDING PRIVACY PRINCIPLES
77Agency Limited ("We") are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy.
This policy (together with our terms of use at this website and any other documents
referred to on it or we have agreed with you for the provision or our services and
products through our site) sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect from
you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us. Please read the following
carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data and how we
will treat it.
Use of this website is subject to the following terms and conditions which you are
deemed to accept by continuing to browse these pages. If you do not agree to these
terms and conditions, please leave this site now.
By submitting your information you consent to the use of your Data as set out in this
Policy. Any information that you give us is held with the utmost care and security. It will
not be used in ways to which you have not consented.
For the purpose of the Data Protection Act 1998 (the Act), the data controller is Legal
Department, 77Agency Limited of 2nd Floor 40-42 Parker Street, London, United Kingdom,
WC2B 5PQ , telephone +44 (0) 207 831 5392] and email privacy@77agency.com.
INFORMATION WE MAY COLLECT FROM YOU
We may collect and process the following data about you:
        Information that you provide by filling in forms on this website (our site). This
         includes information provided at the time of registering to use our site,
         subscribing to our service, posting material or requesting further services. We
         may also ask you for information when you report a problem with our site.
        If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence.
        We may also ask you to complete surveys that we use for research purposes,
         although you do not have to respond to them.
        Details of transactions you carry out through our site.
        Details of your visits to our site including, but not limited to, traffic data, location
         data, weblogs and other communication data, whether this is required for our
         own billing purposes or otherwise and the resources that you access.
        Third parties’ credentials and data necessary to use or interact with our services
         (e.g. Facebook credentials).

IP ADDRESSES AND COOKIES
We may collect information about your computer, including where available your IP
address, operating system and browser type, for system administration and to report
aggregate information to our advertisers. This is statistical data about our users'
browsing actions and patterns, and does not identify any individual.
For the same reason, we may obtain information about your general internet usage by
using a cookie file which is stored on the hard drive of your computer, if you agree.
Cookies contain information that is transferred to your computer's hard drive. They help
us to improve our site and to deliver a better and more personalised service. They enable
us:
        To estimate our audience size and usage pattern.
        To store information about your preferences, and so allow us to customise our
         site according to your individual interests.
        To speed up your searches.
        To recognise you when you return to our site.
You can block cookies by activating the setting on your browser which allows you to
refuse the setting of cookies. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to
access certain parts of our site.
Please note that our advertisers may also use cookies, over which we have no control.
WHERE WE STORE YOUR PERSONAL DATA
The data that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination
outside the European Economic Area ("EEA"). It may also be processed by our staff
operating outside the EEA who work for us or for one of our suppliers. Such staff maybe
engaged in, among other things, the fulfilment of your order, the processing of your
payment details and the provision of support services. By submitting your personal data,
you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. We will take all steps reasonably
necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy
policy.
Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to
access certain parts of our site, you are responsible for keeping this password
confidential. We ask you not to share a password with anyone.
Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure.
Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the
security of your data transmitted to our site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once
we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to
try to prevent unauthorised access.

USES MADE OF THE INFORMATION
We use information held about you in the following ways:
      To ensure that content from our site is presented in the most effective manner
       for you and for your computer.
      To provide you with information, products or services that you request from us or
       which we feel may interest you, where you have consented to be contacted for
       such purposes.
      To carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into between you
       and us.
      To allow you to participate in interactive features of our service, when you
       choose to do so.
      To notify you about changes to our service.
We do not disclose information about identifiable individuals to any third party, but we
may provide third party with aggregate information for statistical purposes. We may also
use such aggregate information to help reach the kind of audience we want to target and
promote our products and services in a more efficient way.
DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATION
We may disclose your personal information to any member of our group, which means
our subsidiaries, our ultimate holding company and its subsidiaries.
We may disclose your personal information to third parties:
      In the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we may
       disclose your personal data to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or
       assets.
      If 77Agency Limited or substantially all of its assets are acquired by a third party,
       in which case personal data held by it about its customers will be one of the
       transferred assets.
      If we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply
       with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our terms of use at our
       site and other agreements; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of
       77Agency Limited, our customers, or others. This includes exchanging
       information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud
       protection and credit risk reduction.
YOUR RIGHTS

You have the right to ask us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes.
We will usually inform you (before collecting your data) if we intend to use your data for
such purposes or if we intend to disclose your information to any third party for such
purposes. You can also exercise the right at any time by contacting us at 2nd Floor 40-42
Parker Street, London, United Kingdom, WC2B 5PQ or email us at
privacy@77agency.com.
Our site may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of our partner
networks, advertisers and affiliates. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please
note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any
responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before you submit
any personal data to these websites.
ACCESS TO INFORMATION
The Act gives you the right to access information held about you. Your right of access can
be exercised in accordance with the Act. Any access request may be subject to a fee of
£10 to meet our costs in providing you with details of the information we hold about you.
CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY
Any changes we may make to our privacy policy in the future will be posted on this page
and it shall be deemed to have become effective at the date it was posted. You are
encouraged to check this Privacy and Security Policy regularly to see whether changes to
this Policy may affect you,
CONTACT
Questions, comments and requests regarding this privacy policy are welcomed and
should be addressed to 2nd Floor 40-42 Parker Street, London, United Kingdom, WC2B
5PQ or email us at privacy@77agency.com.
